{
  "LANGHINDI": 18,
  "qu1": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following statement is correct for a non-reactive systems at steady state?</p>",
      "OPT1": "The rate of accumulation is zero.",
      "OPT2": "The rate of input is zero.",
      "OPT3": "The rate of consumption is zero.",
      "OPT4": "The rate of generation is zero.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu2": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A solution of specific gravity 1.0 consist of 35% A by weight and the remaining B. If the specific gravity of A is 0.7, the specific gravity of B is</p>",
      "OPT1": "1.25",
      "OPT2": "1.3",
      "OPT3": "1.35",
      "OPT4": "1.2",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu3": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Calculate the percent excess air used in the combustion, if the or sat analysis of the flue gas is given as CO<sub>2</sub> = 12.7%, O<sub>2</sub> = 7.1%, N<sub>2</sub> = 80.2%. The Nitrogen present in the flue gas is contributed by air only</p>",
      "OPT1": "58.1%",
      "OPT2": "66.67%",
      "OPT3": "50%",
      "OPT4": "74.2%",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu4": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Pure methane is burnt with 20% excess air then, find the composition of CO<sub>2</sub> in the flue gases is</p>",
      "OPT1": "6.84%",
      "OPT2": "8.04%",
      "OPT3": "10.6%",
      "OPT4": "9.04%",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu5": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following statement about tie component is correct?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Material which remains completely unchanged during the process.",
      "OPT2": "Material which completely consume during the reaction.",
      "OPT3": "Material which consume to a little extent during the reaction.",
      "OPT4": "It is a material which enhance the rate of formation of intermediate.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu6": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A fuel gas have pure methane and it is burnt with pure oxygen, then the min amount of oxygen required for burning per kg of fuel gas is ________ [kg O<sub>2</sub>/kg fuel].</p>",
      "OPT1": "4",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "znhkQSpRhMmrD25WN956iw==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu7": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Na<sub>2</sub>SO<sub>4</sub> \u22c5 10 H<sub>2</sub>O crystals are formed by cooling 100 kg of 30% by weight aqueous solution of Na<sub>2</sub>SO<sub>4</sub>. The final concentration of the Na<sub>2</sub>SO<sub>4</sub> in the solution is ________, if 58.65 kg of crystals formed.</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.10",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "sZ08w+it1r8m4a5ypSA5zg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu8": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The volume occupied by 20 kg of chlorine gas at pressure of 100 kPa and temperature 298 K is ________ (in m<sup>3</sup>).\u00a0</p>\r\n\r\n<p>(Rounded off to nearest integer)</p>",
      "OPT1": "7",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Ar43856SW+87QUodxAaDDw==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu9": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following statement is/are correct?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Incomplete combustion of fuel means it is forming co-instead of CO<sub>2</sub>.",
      "OPT2": "Incomplete burning of fuel means some fuel left un-burnt.",
      "OPT3": "Percent excess is based on 100% completion of the limiting reactant.",
      "OPT4": "Percent excess is based on 100% consumption of non-limiting reactant.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "1tsLNxDzUM4tAESa/gW9mQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "1tsLNxDzUM4tAESa/gW9mQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu10": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>10 kg of A is fed to a batch reactor, where reaction takes place and product B form. If molecular weight of A and B are <em>M<sub>A</sub></em> and <em>M<sub>B</sub></em> respectively, then which of the following statement is correct?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Total number of moles decreases as reaction proceed if <em>M<sub>A</sub></em> > <em>M<sub>B</sub></em>.",
      "OPT2": "Total number of moles increase if <em>M<sub>A</sub></em> < <em>M<sub>B</sub></em>.",
      "OPT3": "Total number of moles decrease if <em>M<sub>A</sub></em> < <em>M<sub>B</sub></em>.",
      "OPT4": "Total number of moles are constant, does not depend on the <em>M<sub>A</sub></em> and <em>M<sub>B</sub></em>.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu11": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Equal masses of CO and N<sub>2</sub> are mixed together in a container at 300 K. The total pressure was found to be 405.3 kPa, the partial pressure of CO gas is</p>",
      "OPT1": "206.45 kPa",
      "OPT2": "198.66 kPa",
      "OPT3": "202.65 kPa",
      "OPT4": "209.46 kPa",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu12": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A solution contain 15% of salt by weight and rest water, 80% of the solution is sent to the evaporator and later mix with 20% of solution to finally obtain product with 35% sucrose, the value of kg H<sub>2</sub>O remove per kg of solution is</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.531",
      "OPT2": "0.427",
      "OPT3": "0.652",
      "OPT4": "0.571",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu13": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>1 kg of saturated aqueous solution of the heavy soluble component (<em>A</em>) at 60\u00b0C, is cooled to 25\u00b0C.<br />\r\nThe solubility of <em>A</em> are 0.6 (kg of <em>A</em>/kg) water at 60\u00b0C and 0.2 (kg <em>A</em>/kg) water at 25\u00b0C, then the amount of crystal formed in kg is</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.25",
      "OPT2": "0.50",
      "OPT3": "0.75",
      "OPT4": "1 kg",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu14": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The ground nut seeds containing 45% oil and 45% solids are fed to expeller, the cake coming out of expeller is found to be containing 80% solids and 5% oil, the percent recovery of oil ________.<br />\r\n(Rounded off to two decimal place)</p>",
      "OPT1": "93.75",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "iORlfKHlxQp94Yh5bB16YA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu15": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A feed stream containing 20% inert, 80% <em>A</em> by mole is fed to a industry whose flow sheet is given a below (<em>A</em> \u2192 3<em>B</em>) takes place in reactor and the separator separate all the product <em>B</em>. The overall (<em>X<sub>A</sub></em>) conversion of the <em>A</em> is 90%, the value of (<em>R</em>/<em>F</em>) is _________. (Rounded off to one decimal place) If one pass conversion in the reactor is 30%.</p>\r\n\r\n<div>\u00a0</div>\r\n\r\n<div><img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAZIAAACdCAYAAACeo/6bAAAgAElEQVR4Xu2deUAV1R7Hv5nPrIgWzS0t8klqYqnIy8pKTI3UJwrxcqGE3EMEwQUxFVQQF0AEVyJAyQ0RwUxTDPT5UjPMl1IaPqVcwl2JSA3hnZl7wcvlwp0Ld5l75jf/FDhzzu/3Pb85H84yv/NAObtAFylACpACpAApUEcFHiCQ1FE5eowUIAVIAVJAVIBAQoFACpACpAApUC8FCCT1ko8eJgX4U8DumRaiUwUXCvlzjjwyiQIEEpPISoWSAtarQJ1BUpyPvWsWwDfyS5QI7ndbgD0Z3rBvUJsWxTga5Qa3yB/YTS/BL3MrJjvaWES80twoOA1ahBuatdv0R0BKGCZ2vYiYbgMQc439Y5Np2Ho0AN0aWsRMWVZKIJFls5BRpIBlFKiAiMEjkrJfsG3CGHzxahSWejnARvh53kF0mjVUGkiyh0mAjhk0KUzHaMfN6JmTCC/72wxyXnDLG4lDCUPQAmroJbkQSLSagkBihtikKkgBa1GgziAROuB+Z/GxwX+pqzvnvAnqztqySomjEm8gQfSjDEXZc/DWnt7YF+4MW5SicJsfesz+O4GEQGLZQKXaSQE5K1AvkDgmoMXySAQNbg/pk1PVQVJWmIvM9Wk429YRN1dOR/KJYsBhDJbGTcVg+8YozE1F3PyrcEv1Y5393ao/385HzpZExP7cBi6XEhB2ZDjr9EfjsX+nITkiDClVyrLVagoVKHp/+x4Ohb+FBvkZWJx4GQMnecOpRSN2rxokCd3lMXqSUSDRiERGjUGmkAKWVEATIhV2SF9wL0L+3kQs/HgBsli/f7/j1+6stT2sCpKmlesUNuj40SokhvZBs8vfIG7mJERdHo6QN3YhJIatp4jrFGOBZer1FeHnb9/Cvn+o1zEcZmBral/8MHoX2oy5Ad8lTZGS5otuNkWq6apsVx0w0FyvEXz4CCET3eEywBEtxHUeNUi295HF6MmSsaJdN4FETq1BtpACFlSgfiDRMLzsInLmjIXXxVESOlwdI5L8RAzptQG9KhfeVVNMPTyvIzw3Ej0OBWpML2lNNzU4hSRXBhPnTTgS4IiGuIqc4EHwSj5TVVldC+ZlwrPjcTogFfOdmwLFJ5DkNxbpbyQi3as9GhBIaoxOAokFX1yqmhSQkwJGAwm01xZq81LHGom44L0SnbRBEtUWGRkf4LFMzXUK7XWLc9g26l2EdkpWg0T1c3DzWDZdJaxz1HIVZeMTpzVo94Ww0N6Y3aiybRQWqMuiEUlN6hFI5PQmky2kgAUVEEAiTGUZvE4i/CU/6TBeX/Yh26FVhmK2thARkIV2SxbAqz3rusW/7H1x4J9r8engNloe1gSSMGDaMsz3fY1NbWUhdGQcELQCc5yb4bKw4D39QSzNXoLBtj+zsr0QIq6FsAXyaiOSu7i4bQr6+JyBW8X6DdumvP+UDXo6tmSjjPtXmTgS+g7euTEYzOayVH4cQPfVCzC4Fa2R1BaaBBILvrhUNSkgRwUM/o5E3PrrDv8vzovuPOIyA7FB3njbnkFEmOaK3YrvL+1C3j9WGgCSWbjgYIufTpxh5c1Bctgo9YI3A9WpFPgPmiauxQj/Nr9TNgIi91eT8snAHaqRRNlvOPp5LGYGfYaf2DaAjiNDETbJA93EBXT1JY5GhiFFWN9RX1X8EH9Hu7ZoRCLHN5ZsIgVkqIDBIKnRB2E0sBRb2gxDz32+WNE21gCQaE5tyUUkAgmBRC6xSHaQAjJXwGggqfZXflP0Wb5TCybqqS3NDxKrrZHIRTD6IJFAIpdYJDtIAZkrYDSQVPopdMCetY9INFKk+NmmsrWKeHROyVTtnpLDVZqLaEqRUmNL0BqJHIKUbCAFZKSAcUGi2jXlv+sq81DXiKSq41XzXVk295aMmkT2phBIZN9EZCApYF4FjAsS89pOtVlGAQKJZXSnWkkB2SpAIJFt08jWMAKJbJuGDCMFLKMAgcQyultzrQQSa249sp0UMIECBBITiMp5kQQSzhuY3CMFDFWAQGKoYnQ/gYRigBQgBaooQCChgDBUAQKJoYrR/aQA5woQSDhvYBO4RyAxgahUJClgzQoQSKy59SxjO4HEMrpTraSAbBUgkMi2aWRrGIFEtk1DhpECllGAQGIZ3a25VrOApGrag6pyVaZ6rpeKwhkIWYiPyMLzYeHsLIGGOkorwqmkZfiq80RMcmwoHljjJub30bza4l9z3NGo0TsI8nIw4Nzpehlv8MO6DiAyuBB6QKcC0o+WtQ4BzRkrvGlnHS0sDyvNAhLRVXXSs7Ve6jMCxF/FwPO4C9aLx1jW9VKndvZJA2zGIOlIKHrZapcmpLOegQlnhuLzACc1IFSZPD2vzlCfnCac6paIjNYD0Wn7VMS3nYflg5+rh1119Uf/c0LnkH3gG/030h0GKeDc8zXxYCeeLnPFCo/a8RQHpvbFzCAZiby599NIlxUew4Hf2+JN4QCcel16zgkQ0ln3TEf3XexENfGkM+ESznL2QPQLq9TnMd83QDwpbeAZTNYJpXoZapSHzdU5GMVYKyqEx87QXLHCo3ZWFLoWN9VyIBFGKP6/YljcELRAEfKz05AcEYaUE+yIMocxWBo3FYPtbdiU1T5sSYxESPJ3TKzu8Kw4LlM49SxzA1ZMX8ROSnsJfVyArCMuquM2q8xs3UZ+kjf6pvXDngxvdhSoWnNxhDQDSNyKyY42VRtCODrUdTxOB6TKJ421hoXm6hwsHp1mNoDHztBcscKjdmYOP6uuzswgGYCYaxp6uazEoQRXPJI9Bz0imiIlzRfdbIrYlJMX3LJdsWedHZJfiUGT9Umss7dFcW4sPAYdwvt7Q/BEtDdWN5uLxNA+aFFyCtvCA9lRn711gEQYeQzC5KaxqmM3K6oXD8+ZgKxKc9rCs/L8A9UzHyNMPe0lrzY2V+cgL69Nbw2PnaG5YoVH7UwfcfzUYGaQaExtVY5I3sBJ1ml7JZ+pqmqTACRE/g5fr3iUVPkXdkbB8mHI89mATpkVo4naprZU5yGEdkquAhJxA0DIk9isOUqprEd9ElreBAY6YcQkr8tcnYO8vDa9NTx2huaKFR61M33E8VOD5UBSqaGqow9uHqv1178aDtOfqraALq5h9NqAXnUGiars3t++V8OIg0DCT4hL94THzpBAIr396c66K2BmkLyPnIAdWovbwo6qKejjcwZuFesfxfnYf8oGr7U8BF/nqShwX4xlwa6wtylG/r4zeKzrX9jgMQzxrWcjPcYT7fEjkvy8EHLgXR27tnRNbQm/G46UfyRonR9dIaT2jq66C2yKJ83VOZjCdjmXSSCpe+vwqF3d1VDek2YBSbXvSMS1EY0pI2Hh/PNYzAz6DD+xzbkdR4YibJIHurE5pcLcVMQFz1Evwn+EeeG+GOHYHCX5GYiYOJX9Huz+cEx/YS+8ZmYATaZprZMI23rZGkxUW2SI01iaR3+yBte2RYgBcbHdG4dHbZDlFmACiWleVB47Q3PFCo/amSbK+CzVLCCxuHTC9l+nNWj3RSK87BvrNYe2/+qViMsbeOwMCSRchqrsnFIGSKDrg8Sa2uIm2zU2iT5IlF2omt4gAkndNeZRu7qrobwnFQISoWE1U6Q8UUNLs1QrufGIOP667FOkGPfL9nu4snse/jV3d3Vd2nkgOGQM+tppfWvD4bvCY2dIIxIOA1WGLikIJDJUv44mmapzuHciAW7j/w3XVSvwkcMjKLtyFOsi5yHpmicSV7vDru55bKp5WnblGyybmgjbKTFiXXK4CCR1bwUetau7Gsp7kkBihW1uKpCwYQmCh6xHOzVIgDsoSAvChIL3kRrYw7hJLMW6voFz+iz0ffpBWbQCj52hyWJFq8V41E4WQWklRhBIrKShNM00WedQBSSNUVKQhTVp19H7Q3e89PTfmAll7HffYmdaAuLS89jPnfDP2TMwvp8dUPANNq6KxLoDl4CHe2Pi6iC4t2XTYWVXkJeVic8XJ+Dgn+yRjoFIjO6K/NULEC6Wof7d6kF49McvsW5JLLafFj5BZWUH+uID15fw9O0CHN65BWsLWuLNK1uw6vhAxGWOQicj84fHztBksUIgscKew3QmE0hMp63JSjZZ5yCCZC2eGGKH7PSvgSFRVUcixYcQNSSZpadZyKajbFByYi18x/8X/VP8YJv+X9j7ucIOF7Fntg/CSydgc7gDjs32x8Ym/ojwew1P4wzS/PejQ7QXOl3XHJE8oCpr8mn0FwH0EK4cWoOgKVl4JngU2iwPx/pbTM52YxEX15NlQjigKoNAojfGTBYrBBK92ivpBpOCxJxnISip0QRfjbvYrlavckSyEL1OxcIn+ho8VgnQELIzs40Ih2LgMSUVt6uI/QI+WBWHoTY/4j+njiN7iXrk0TMEmwOB6CpTZRoPVpnauoO8hI8xMX84Nkf0Y8ARrhs4HDkOIQhA6uRm+GrcWKztsRRbRznAyPyoNEoYkfB46Y+Ve7iesxi+m8rg5jcJ7h0M31jB42iOx1gwlU8mBYmpjDZFuQL0rOUsCpP9lVllaquUde7TMXFjE/U01cOqnV2LH0dEuh9esbm/8l52aTdCPFeidOgEjBj0DyDTX4TCxvG/Y47nJrywZDUCejxZpdnKCtLwsedxuItrJHpAEvgcDgaNQpz9IpODxFpiQOo7IDVWSs99idAp5/DeunF4ueKkBVxH7u5zsO/3MvQd9EAgkdoifN5HIFG3K4EE0N61hbJLOBzzCYK+fBbBKUF4G9kMGItwwWUaZk3oA7tHSlDwbQHKSvfAZ9qvGJ0SgSGP5t3f6RVtj68nBmAdBlTbQqyq6wQ+ZM+42/1NNdqZBYSIkAJKzmRg/rjdaCdMo714FWlmGpEoEyTluH16Dz79dD0O3umINx2aQlgRE0aFeee7IGhOH/UoseZOkEDCJyCkekUgIZAwBbS/I3kCr85OQHi/lqxH/xlpc6cjTlzg/hDNftJYEG/nBr8pIzGweT7ips5GxunH8OpofzjfTUT42p+BnrORON4GX1cswrOaGvcKQdLcfmgONaTSzqKtdxRiR7XF5d3xmDc3la2ksEtd9qCOl5A0aCzWCWsk7LL1XmOyUQmPnaHUEUn5+Qz4j0tHw84t8FBF71F+C2cfHIJl4RXTjQQSqR2r0u4jkBBIlBbzNfqrZJDg7glszGgID48OGmtQl7FvYz46D30dT+mJEh61oxdDugIEEgKJ9Gjh/E4eO0OpI5L6Ni2P2tVXEyU9TyAhkCgp3mv1lcfO0BCQlF7/CTk7duGbvGtoZOcE54Fv45XW0nZw8agdvRjSFSCQEEikRwvnd/LYGUoGye08pEwMRGppF7zVwx5P/K0Ipw8Wo8fMQAx6Xn8KGx614zzcjeoegYRAYtSAsubCeOwMpYFE+EYoFr7HXsfSMd3xeMWHOsXfIz6+CO6T36I1EmsObDPYTiAhkJghzKyjCuWCRNi1txzbW43WSqB5ATuD9+LZeR/qzSLAo3bWEbXysJJAQiCRRyTKwAoeO0NpIxLgr5MbMf9IRwQOZx8fCiOSe7dQsG8dwne2Reii/mj5QO0NxKN2MghJqzGBQEIgsZpgNbWhPHaGUkGC8qv4bvkszP+uEV5kR1xfOn4UZ4odMCwmHGO7VM1KoKsdeNTO1PHGU/kEEgIJT/FcL1947Aylg+Q6Tv37FIob38LpExfx1+NtYG/3DJ7p0AGtH9V/EA2P2tUrmBT2MIGEQKKwkK/ZXR47Q8kguXcCnw0/jFfWa6Tn/20nZsU/BN9ZvdGMprboPalFAQIJgYReELUCygNJOf48kYqIzEI816wYuann0MajeyU07p47gNS83lix8QO015NymUft6MWQrgCBhEAiPVo4v5PHzlDviOSPE9i0ZD3+++cfuJRXiMYvPo/HK0YfDZ7Ci24jMbR7czTU0/Y8asd5uBvVPQKJlYLEqFFAhVUqoMzsv4L7JTj9VS4a9n0DdpVLIiW4cPoWmrZreT+RYw2xQiBR9ktEILFCkCg7ZMl7QxTQOyKpLOwurp88iJwj/8PNu+Xq3/6O05ccMDmY0sgborkS7yWQEEiUGPeK8VkqSMrOZSDAMxaFLR7H7Ydbq7YAny3CU/18MGtUdzrYSjERUzdHCSQEkrpFDj1lFQpIA4nwZXsYAs8Nwer+5zA3tRlmT+qKu4c3Y9tDLhhJ35FYRVtb0kgCCYHEkvFHdZtYAWkgYbu3jiUi4uI7CHUpwabAb+CwgKVFubETU6cXYVzSULTT8ykJrZGYuCFlXjyBhEAi8xAl8+qjgDSQsBpK/4et4Vvw16Bh6HYyGlN33cPf2VmVx2zHIGmpK9oQSOrTDNw/SyAhkHAf5Ep2UDJImEj3Sm6iCDZ4stEtnMzZi4O/PYpuLn3x8tON9EpIIxK9EnF9A4GEQMJ1gCvdOWkguYfrOYvhu6kMbn6T4N5B2mFWmtoSSJQdaQQSAomy3wDOvZcGEjazde5LhE45h/fWjcPLlQOQ68jdfQ72/VhGYD06EUg4DyQ97hFICCTKfgM4914aSMpx+/QefPrpehy80xFvOjTF30RdbiDvfBcEzaHvSDgPk3q7RyAhkNQ7iKgA+SogDSRA+fkM+I9LR8POLe5/xV5+C2cfHIJl4f3wNI1I5NvIMrCMQEIgkUEYkgmmUkAqSHD3BDZmNISHRwfcz894Gfs25qPz0NfpqF1TNRAn5RJICCSchDK5oUsBySDRKR/l2qKokqYAgYRAIi1S6C6rVEA6SCjXllU2sEyMJpAQSGQSimSGKRSQChLKtWUK9ZVTJoGEQKKcaFegp9JAQrm2FBgaRnWZQEIgMWpAUWHyUkAaSCjXlrxazfqsIZAQSKwvasliyQpIAwkrjnJtSdaUbqyuAIGEQELvBccKSAYJ04BybXEcCCZ2jUBCIDFxiFHxllTAEJDgzmWcOvYjfv3zYbRq1wEdWj+u8U1J7V5QihRLtrLl6yaQEEgsH4VkgckUkAySO/9DZuh0RO+/qLalFV6fHIYZ7u3xqATrCCQSROL4FgIJgYTj8CbXpIGkDMWHYuCx4A4mLRmD3vZN0PCPizi+YyfOdB0KN3v9KCGQKDvWCCQEEmW/AZx7Lw0kQhr5BfA+ORCp47ugMvnv3WNYE/wL3l1EB1txHib1do9AQiCpdxBRAfJVQBpIWNLG64exOvkPuPn3RrMH1P7cPICFPmcxeO0HaM8ScJUVHEAOnNDb7qFqDtOIRL4xYA7LCCQEEnPEGdVhIQWkgUSVRj7h0y340bYLHJsLoChHSf7XSDv7LNz72eMR9pu75/6Hh977BN4Owk9VLwKJhRpYJtUSSAgkMglFMsMUCkgDSQ1p5LUMKr91By/4hBFITNFQVl4mgYRAYuUhTObXpoBUkKjSyDfAoHea407Dx/HkIw2rFXvv5A5sQ292FO/DNCKhsKuiAIGEQEKvBMcKSAZJ+VUcS1qEkIQDuDMkCqmBTrh7YD222wzEyC5P6lWIprb0SsT1DQQSAgnXAa5056SBhK2RnEiGf8qDGOFhi/9sexij5rFTEYsPIXphEUaw/2+mR0gCibIjjUBCIFH2G8C599JAImT/jcXWZqMwrvMv+GzeRfwzhIGEbf9dPSIXPTeOQqf7xybqVIxAwnkg6XGPQEIgUfYbwLn30kAC/HVyM5b92hMBb19HoggSZzx4aA18E1ogbLU77BrULhSBhPNAIpBIa2DhhSu4UCjtZrqLFLASBaSCBOW/IWf+fGxv1AS3f/gTbexv4mDWLXSfH4NPerVExaclNblNILGSgDCRmTQioRGJiUKLipWDApJBIhhb8isO79mJ7MNnUWzzPJzefhd9X3lW/IZE30Ug0acQ3/9OICGQ8B3hCveudpD8gcKCm2hg8xgeb2qLh/A7CnK2YtPufJQ/+wr6uvaBY8vqW311SUogUXagEUgIJMp+Azj3vjaQlJ/PQEDkb+gzwAkvv9ENrS5uhY/XUlx88R307/4ofjl4F87z/NG3ZfWUKNqyEUg4DyRaI5HWwLRGIk0nusu6FKgZJGW4dWAFVmMopvVsypwSdm7Nw78W22Be6mT0fOJBlF7chYitTeE/sTts9LhNILGuuDC2tTQioRGJsWOKypORAjWDRADHcmxvNRofibmzbuP0xikYs9cZiZW7tC5gZ8h+tJ01TEzaWNtFIJFRo1vAFAIJgcQCYUdVmkuBmkFSjj+/W4N5lwcgrH9rtivrBg5HjkPQldHYHMG+IREN/A17QrLQatYH9B2JuRrMSushkBBIrDR0yWwpCtS62H47DynTPscfb7+JZ0u+x5ZVu3Bvwqf4bKg9xM9GhDTyIdcwItoVrfXs/6URiZTW4PceAgmBhN/oJs+gb/tv6eVvsXFlPFL3/IanB4xH0KT+aPdoGa58l4Gt+37Cn47emNTrGRVYarkIJMoONgIJgUTZbwDn3usDibHcJ5AYS0nrLIdAQiCxzsglqyUpQCCRJBPdVE8FCCQEknqGED0uZwUIJHJuHX5sI5AQSPiJZvKkmgIEEgoKcyhAICGQmCPOqA4LKUAgsZDwCquWQEIgUVjIK8tdAomy2ttS3hJICCSWij2q1wwKEEjMIDJVAQIJgYReA44VIJBw3Lgyco1AQiCRUTiSKcZWgEBibEWpPF0KEEgIJPRmcKwAgYTjxpWRawQSAomMwpFMMbYCBBJjK0rl0Yiklhig80joBeFRAQIJj60qP59oREIjEvlFJVlkNAUIJEaTkgqqRQECCYGEXhCOFSCQcNy4MnKNQEIgkVE4kinGVoBAYmxFqTxaI6E1EnoLFKaAABJzXQUXCs1VFdUjMwVoREIjEpmFJJljaQUq4ENgsHRLWE/9BBICifVEK1lqFgUIJGaRmatKCCQEEq4CmpypvwIEkvprqLQSCCQEEqXFPPmrRwECCYWIoQoQSAgkhsYM3c+5AgQSzhvYBO4RSLgGyTlsG/Uu/Hdd1QodG3QcuRjLgl1hb9PABGGlo8iy33A0cwMSf3kL0X6OaGhIrcUnkBT+H7wU7I1WWZPRwyet6tM2/RGQEoaJTg/jWEwcfnCZBK/2tobUQPdqKEAgoXAwVAECCdcgEZwrxtEoN7gluWDr0QB0a3gXhUcS8IlnJK7M2IF0r/YwPUruA+3JwB04EmAASMp+wbYJs3B27DJMdnxCbK3S3Cg4Db+B6COh6GVbjFNJUzEkqj1SBP9uH0H0sI14fvUCDG7VyND3ge5nChBIKAwMVYBAwj1ISlG4zQ89Zv9dDRLmcNkpJLmOx+mAVMx3bmpozNTxfhVMQjslGwCSMhRlz8FbG7thx8ohaCUST+1PQnfsyfCGPfudCBZvIEEE5W3kJ3nD9eexOBTuDBqXGN5cBBLDNVP6EwQSxYGkCPnbliOZTTFN9H0NLcTOmf0uOw3JEWFIOVEMOIzB0ripGGzfGIW5O7BhRRhidp1n9zljZlgHrJi5EjeEx1xW4tDqZ7Gh2wDEXFP/nDAA0HomJCcRXvZXqoKkOB85WxKxcOZn+Ak1TLWJwHNHunuaxshJNcIahQUMSF1xOz8L8REh2N0pBqkBTqwkxsn8RAwZeAaTxRGL6cdbvHUiBBLeWtT0/hBIFAMSwLPv90jZyP6bkqkxElH91d8joilS0nzRzaaIddRecMvuhwSvk/Bd0wwrkqehV4sy9pf+THzRORST7Y/gk57p6L5riTh9VJa/Fj7bO2JxwMso2jYFfVbqeMbxhgZInsOBYA8sbLpI1fkXs+kod2/kDNMEhsC3bHzitABN1m9l01oCIipGUyOwr/NbuJ78Of6L7vCMmIOJI5zUUKx4biawStNP079MvNRAIOGlJc3nB4FEMSBhU1v7++GHQC+EnP8AW0VoCH+tX0VO8CB4JZ+pGnVNnNHH4Thyu+uaihKe8UD0C6vYSKE5jkUtwg//nF191FGlRI2prdFFCHEahhQ2+NG8qq2fFKZjtONKdMrUAIkIlzVo90UMXv3PLAw96KIx7aUurTQX0d1GIm/uTnw6uI353iZOaiKQcNKQZnSDQKIkkFQsRrsPQ3zr2UiP8UR7mwviSCG4eWzVNQVxWmkAFnWO17HWoB7FRLVFxjo7pEQCgfPYekStz2iAZPivGO+4GC2qjIx0RL0OkFSZtrJhZU4Yg6/ejcfywc/d3zRAIKlXF0IgqZd8inyYQMI9SLR3bbE1hMIshI4cj1S7xchaydY0Mtl0lM8ZuC2PRNDg9myqKR/7T/2Fh/cFwyOyFJ4Vv9d8RcTpqCiUvtMOxV39ECou2t9UTYvpfEYDJP5N8cUEd/gXvKtei7FBcf4R/PxYV3RrobHTqtrUlmohvW+UU+XGgbKL6fBxTkCThWrbBRtFkPjiWgxNbdWlVyOQ1EU1ZT9DIOEaJNrfkbhjaW4MBrMV9uJTKfAfNA2549h2XP9W+OHzWMwMqlj4DkXYJA829fUL9q5ZAN/IL1Ei6GTzLyzNVq2LAOpOPa1f5e4pUUoGoerP+AGzXCu/ZxGmsA4PL8OmZaGYlfwde0jHOodYmOYU2jNsCo1tY478QdViNmOQJC6ml+KisC7jsxklwuJ/whA0Exfbv4d3pa3KfskN9Z5AYqhidD+BhGuQmDbASxmUPI+7YL3JvkXRmEJTb/XV7xFt/9WvUe13EEjqq6DynieQEEjqGPVsGitmA4q8x5l2i62ODxJrNViYcqMPEuvYpqrHCCT1kk+RDxNICCR1CPwyNjW2ARG7XkCQn+rbDZNelSlSxqh3mtVUmwA3SpFS17bQdQgWnUlSVzWV9RyBhEBiWMSLC+Bs667dRCSJ35dQGhLDBJTv3QQS+baN3C0jkBBI5B6jZJ+ZFCCQmEloDqshkBBIOAxrcqmuCmjDhJupLfGbpAnIqiZMTTsG66qgMp8jkBBIlBn55LVOBTRBwg1EKjwVvy8agLVeFRmohbxzizHJZy8c9X0cS/FSqwIEEgIJvSKkQKUCyiuWM0QAAANYSURBVAIJc5s+XjVK9BNICCRGCaSKQmie3ahymr0wawBJnaffdIxIxLNsFrAko0dmokN+GuLmX4Vbqp/q3J7cVI2f1Rmyl+Wj7bvXsCT0LMYIOeC6/o6jmh/zfrQKiaF9WAJRtrMxfx+2JEYipOKjW10ZIszewqapkECiARLTSEylkgKkgDkVqHFKrgIknmH4+N8LEHa0GI+4zEBskAee3C6k9mFZE5pMY+l3xgLL1FkUtH9GD/hlrsTA40tYJuwZ7L++6Luhh5gEtUtRBkvXMwE7K5ORCvcmsczVtijOjYXHoEN4XzxSobE55TBLXQQSAolZAo0qIQXMqYBOmFQbkWhapH0AnPbP1fO8VWbOzn1flU0bbA2GJURd+84G7O2aiZ6e8arUQpXXSwwsGpmszSmIiesikJhYYCUVT9NaSmpty/la5zirF0h0nDQKYfoqAxETp6oOhBMPaBPy1LHTPA9NRY/pT6nzwfF/uBqBxHLvA/c1Cy88dzt/uG81+TtY57iSApLpD6oSk9r+jCQ/dnbPkeHqTNO6RiRMq+JT2BaegJvec6tMWamyUk9FgftiLAt2hb1NMfL3ncFjb3S5fwCb/KWWbCGBRLJUdCMpQApYrQLa35GoM0W3qHRISPujyoidxQYXj7jMwfxO2QiI3M/ueBV9XC4ha5f68Ddx3SSALcirj3XuNYOd1Kl5CWsjazAMexAXPEd9fPVHmBfuixGOLe+fm2O1YlY3nEDCUWOSK6QAKWBOBVQ7u1ZuewzjQgehlTCDJZ7TI6yTbMKRAEcw1ijiIpAoopnJSVKAFDC6AmLeOV8ULtQ40lk8JdQd6e5p7Bjq9lyOPnTpSCAxenRRgaQAKaAIBSqOlm5WcWx1MVTfpTyEcIUdqkYgUUTEk5OkAClgfAWEXVtZiI8IRsyu86x4YdfWTEz3dkcve1vjVyfjEgkkMm4cMo0UIAVIAWtQgEBiDa1ENpICpAApIGMFCCQybhwyjRQgBUgBa1CAQGINrUQ2kgKkACkgYwUIJDJuHDKNFCAFSAFrUIBAYg2tRDaSAqQAKSBjBQgkMm4cMo0UIAVIAWtQgEBiDa1ENpICpAApIGMFCCQybhwyjRQgBUgBa1CAQGINrUQ2kgKkACkgYwX+DwDYwjg0KMiYAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" /></div>",
      "OPT1": "5.61",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "m+eY10cqTMjgmj18IR0rrA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu16": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Chlorinated diphenyl is heated from 313 K to 533 K in an indirectly heater at the rate of 4000 kg/hr.<br />\r\nThe heat required to be added to the fluid in the heater (in KW) is ________. (Rounded off to 2 decimal place)<br />\r\nData: <em>C<sub>P</sub></em> = 0.7511 + 1.465 \u00d7 10<sup>\u20133</sup> T, (KJ/kg.K)</p>",
      "OPT1": "335.08",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "WlFyt2uy76++JxvyME3+ag==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu17": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following statement is/are correct?</p>",
      "OPT1": "The specific heats of solids are lower than liquids.",
      "OPT2": "All oxidation reactions are exothermic.",
      "OPT3": "The dissolution of common salt in water is endothermic.",
      "OPT4": "Steam-hydrocarbon reforming reaction is endothermic in nature.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "NW/S2V6ynXPSzqqh6+wP8A==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "NW/S2V6ynXPSzqqh6+wP8A==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "TEST_NAME": "Topicwise Test-19 Part Syllabus GATE 2026 CH Thermodynamics and Process Calculations-3",
  "TEST_ID_ENCODED": "NjQzNDE0Nw==",
  "TEST_ID": "NjQzNDE0Nw=="
}